ACWA "The Advance" Publications 5743 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ACWA "The Advance" Publications
1920-1930
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (ACWA)
5743 PUBS
4 cubic feet
4 linear ft.
Publications (documents).
Collection consists of 12 volumes.
6849703
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, May 17, 2010
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 28, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5619: ACWA Records 5619 PUBS: ACTWU Publications 6352 PUBS: Tom Harriman Collection of Amalgamated Publications
Clothing workers, Labor unions, New York (State).; Collective bargaining, Clothing industry, New York (State).; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America.; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union.
6849703
- The Advance, 1920-1921 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  English and French. v.4:no.2 (1920:Mar. 12) - v.4:no.52 (1921:Feb. 25). Bound volume.
  - Item 1: The Advance, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America)). v.4:no.2 (1920:Mar. 12) - v.4:no.52 (1921:Feb. 25). Bound volume. Item is in English; French.
- The Advance, 1923-1924; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  English and French. v.7:no.1 (1923:Mar. 2) - v.7:no.52 (1924:Feb. 22). Bound volume.
  - Item 1: The Advance, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America)). v.7:no.1 (1923:Mar. 2) - v.7:no.52 (1924:Feb. 22). Bound volume. Item is in English; French.
- The Advance, 1924-1925; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  English and French. v.8:no.1 (1924:Feb. 29) - v.8:no.47 (1925:Mar. 20). Bound volume.
  - Item 1: The Advance, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America)). v.8:no.1 (1924:Feb. 29) - v.8:no.47 (1925:Mar. 20). Bound volume. Item is in English; French.
- The Advance, 1925-1926; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  English and French. v.9:no.1 (1925:Mar. 27) - v.11:no.26 (1926:Dec. 31). Bound volume.
  - Item 1: The Advance, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America)). v.9:no.1 (1925:Mar. 27) - v.11:no.26 (1926:Dec. 31). Bound volume. Item is in English; French.
- The Advance, 1929-1930; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  English and French. v.15:no.3 (1929:Jan. 18) - v.16:no.33 (1930:Aug. 15). Bound volume.
  - Item 1: The Advance, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America)). v.15:no.3 (1929:Jan. 18) - v.16:no.33 (1930:Aug. 15). Bound volume. Item is in English; French.
- Darbas [The Advance], 1920-1922; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Lithuanian. v.3:no.1 (1920:Aug. 20) - v.4:no.26 (1922:Dec. 29). Bound volume.
  - Item 1: Darbas (The Advance), Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America)). v.3:no.1 (1920:Aug. 20) - v.4:no.26 (1922:Dec. 29). Bound volume. Item is in Lithuanian.
- Darbas [The Advance], 1925-1926; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Lithuanian. v.7:no.1 (1925:Jan. 2) - v.8:no.19 (1926:Dec. 24). Bound volume.
  - Item 1: Darbas (The Advance), Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America)). v.7:no.1 (1925:Jan. 2) - v.8:no.19 (1926:Dec. 24). Bound volume. Item is in Lithuanian.
- Darbas [The Advance], 1927-1928; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Lithuanian. v.9:no.1 (1927:Jan. 7) - v.10:no.26 (1928:Dec. 21). Bound volume.
  - Item 1: Darbas (The Advance), Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America)). v.9:no.1 (1927:Jan. 7) - v.10:no.26 (1928:Dec. 21). Bound volume. Item is in Lithuanian.
- Darbas [The Advance], 1929-1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Lithuanian. v.11:no.1 (1929:Jan. 4) - v.12:no.26 (1930:Dec. 26). Bound volume.
  - Item 1: Darbas (The Advance), Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America)). v.11:no.1 (1929:Jan. 4) - v.12:no.26 (1930:Dec. 26). Bound volume. Item is in Lithuanian.
- Forschritt [The Advance], 1925-1926; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Yiddish. v.9:no.1 (1925:Apr. 10) - v.9:no.32 (1926:Mar. 26). Bound volume.
  - Item 1: Forschritt (The Advance), Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America)). v.9:no.1 (1925:Apr. 10) - v.9:no.32 (1926:Mar. 26). Bound volume. Item is in Yiddish.
- Forschritt [The Advance], 1926; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Yiddish. v.12:no.1 (1926:Apr. 2) - v.12:no.38 (1926:Dec. 31). Bound volume.
  - Item 1: Forschritt (The Advance), Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America)). v.12:no.1 (1926:Apr. 2) - v.12:no.38 (1926:Dec. 31). Bound volume. Item is in Yiddish.
- Forschritt [The Advance], 1927; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Yiddish. v.13:no.1 (1927:Jan. 7) - v.13:no.51 (1927:Dec. 30). Bound volume.
  - Item 1: Forschritt (The Advance), Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America)). v.13:no.1 (1927:Jan. 7) - v.13:no.51 (1927:Dec. 30). Bound volume. Item is in Yiddish.